*Your info
	-ID: 1412280
	-Name: Trần Hoàng Lâm
	-Email: malartsoft@gmail.com

*What you have done
	-Completed app Jars

*Link youtube guide: https://youtu.be/u6XF-aMaCUk

*Main flow
	1. Open app Jars
	2. Input money ($) in textbox
	3. Press button to calculator
	4. View result 
	5. Can change size screen by enter File -> setting

*Additional flow
	2.1 If you enter number money so small (<20$), screen show error
	"Number is so small - Try again"

	2.2 If you enter number money is negative, screen show error
	"Don't input number smaller 0 - Try again"

	2.3 if you enter the amount of characters char, screen show error
	"Exist char in textbox - Try again"

	2.4 If you don't enter, screen show error
	"Can't input equal null - Try again"

	2.5 If you enter money is so lagl,screen show error
	"Overflow!! Try again", L"Error"